

ENES EKINCI

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Contact:

+90 537 698 1462



@ enes_9379@hotmail.com

SKILLS

Apache Kafka

Java

Python

C#

Shell scripting

SQL

Docker

PL/pgSQL

Logstash

Elasticsearch

Git

EXPERTIES

- Agile
- Teamwork
- Adaptable
- Innovative
- Helpful
- Fast Learner

FOREIGN LANGUAGES

ENGLISH

Reading

Listening

Writing

Speaking

YDS Exam Result / 2021

• 64 / 100

ABOUT ME

Hello I'm Enes and i freshly graduated the Computer Engineering program of Kocaeli University. I have attended and managed our computer club in 3rd grade. I'm into data engineering, big data and devops. I am an eager person who makes use of all the opportunities I get. I am currently working as Software Development Assistant Specialist in Big Data Department at Innova.

ENES EKINCI

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Contact: (\$\+90 537 698 1462



@ enes_9379@hotmail.com

EDUCATION

• 2019-2024

KOCAELI UNIVERSITY

Bachelor degree of Computer Engineering study program, GPA: 3.33

CAREER SUMMARY

2021-2022

KOCAELI UNIVERSITY COMPUTER SOCIETY

I managed the club as a board member. We organized various events and courses which many students can make use of.

• 07.2022 - 08.2022 INNOVA BİLİŞİM ÇÖZÜMLERİ A.Ş.

I worked as a Big Data Intern. I built a basic data pipeline project with python which takes the data and produces it to kafka, and then consumes it back to the python, manipulates the data and loads it to the specific elasticsearch index. I understood and absorbed the essentials of pub-sub pattern.

• 07.2023 - 08.2023

EXCLUSIVE NETWORKS

I worked as a **Network Security Engineer Intern** in Ankara office. I learnt and applied the basic configurations of several Firewalls(Palo Alto) and Load Balancers(Citrix).

• 2022-2023

INNOVA BİLİŞİM ÇÖZÜMLERİ A.Ş.

Part-time(2 days) Software Development Assistant Specialist at Big Data Department. Working in various projects.

Tech Stack: Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL) Docker PL/SQL Logstash ETL Tools Data Migration, Elasticsearch.

CERTIFICATES

02.2024 - 03.2024

DEVOPS BOOTCAMP TRAINEE

A detailed Devops bootcamp organized by Techcareer.net.

Learned about Git, Docker, Docker swarm, Gitlab, Virtual Machines, Linux, Shell scripting, bash scripting, Infrastructure as code.

Linkedin Profile

linkedin.com/in/enesekinci

Github Profile

github.com/ekincienes